SCREAM THE NAME OF THE PERSON YOU LOVE!
[Taiki sighs]
- [Taiki] The person...
- [gasps]
- [Taiki] ...I like is...
- [Hina sighs]
[both] Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
It's Yusa, meow!
[all] Huh?
When he was sleeping on the bus,
he was mumbling about Yusa.
"Your smashes are fast!"
He likes him so much he dreams about him.
Really?
So he's in a love triangle
with Moriya, meow.
[gasps]
[Kyo] Hm.
[mischievous music playing]
You're goin' down, Inota!
This fight sounds fiercer
than a badminton match!
I'm not fighting her!
[Nishida] Ayame and Taiki
are about to face off!
[Taiki] What? Like, on the court?
It's late. It's time
you all went to sleep.
[Ayame] What? Things were
just getting good, though!
[teacher] Wrap it up! Wrap it up.
Goodnight!
Thanks for earlier.
It's not like anyone expected you
to give a real answer, anyway.
Still, though, I appreciate it.
But you acknowledge...
that you were hesitating.
[gasps]
[Taiki] It's not that I was hesitating.
I'm in love with Chinatsu.
That hasn't changed.
But...
Hina and I...
have had some good moments together
as friends.
REPORT CARDS
STRETCH
And maybe she has made
my heart skip a beat a time or two.
My methodology is to date anybody
who tells me they like me.
[Taiki] Now I get what Ayame was saying.
My head is spinning...
[groans]
[slow instrumental music playing]
and spinning.
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
EPISODE 23
SPINNING
[yawns] I'm so tired.
My entire body is sore.
Three more days of this is gonna be...
hell.
Badminton club! Morning!
Let's get out there and carpe that diem!
How's this dude so hyped up?
Must be a morning person.
[Taiki] I gotta get ready
to focus on practice.
If I let the other stuff get in my head,
this will all be for nothing.
[boy] Hey.
Somebody left this tote bag behind
in the lobby.
Whose is it?
It's Hina's.
She's my friend from gymnastics.
- I can get it to her.
- You sure?
'Cause the gymnastics bus
is heading out it looks like.
[gasps] What?
[Taiki] Hey! Stop the bus!
- Stop the bus!
- [Hina exclaims softly]
[pants]
I'm already out of gas this early?
Here, Hina. You left this behind.
Thanks, Taiki.
See ya!
[inspirational music playing]
[grunting]
Ten more seconds!
[grunts, pants]
[Taiki thuds, racket clatters]
[Nishida] Eat up, lads!
Eat up! Eating is part of training,
you know! [munches loudly]
Eat some of those pickles!
And those shallots, too!
You should have vegetables, too, Nishida--
Don't take my katsu!
[sighs] Could you please be more mindful
of your table manners, guys?
What are you talking about?
During mealtime, we're at war!
The basketball club
doesn't seem to think so.
Hm. Nothing hits the spot
like Japanese rice.
Like, in the U.S., all they eat is steak.
- The vibe is different over there.
- I am not a fan of that handsome laddie.
So you admit that he is handsome, then?
There exist, in this world,
certain facts that cannot be denied.
[groans] Too much!
I like him, actually. Matsuoka.
He hooks me up with great gear.
You game together?
My sister's talked to you about that.
He's good at basketball,
he stays in shape,
and I respect him for that.
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
They'd be a perfect couple.
[Nishida] Who would?
[inspirational music ends]
I'll get a change of clothes.
Okay, dude.
Oh.
GUEST ROOM
Hi, Chinatsu.
Hi, Taiki. How's it--
Huh?
- Hey.
- Huh? Yes?
She hasn't grabbed my shirt in a while.
What did you do to your elbow?
What?
Oh, that...
SKID
I took a spill earlier!
Well, you can't go around
without a bandage on.
[Taiki] I need a bandage?
This is nothing.
Uh... hang on a sec.
[playful music playing]
Do you always carry bandages with you?
I kinda get hurt all the time, so...
[bandage crinkling]
- Now the art!
- A pen?
- [Taiki] Ah, that tickles!
- [Chinatsu] Stop moving!
[pen scratching]
There!
- Water bottle?
- No, it's a boar, silly!
[Nagisa] Huh?
Where's Natsu?
I guess I should get going.
See ya!
[inaudible]
[exclaims softly]
[playful music ends]
UEDA SHIKI HOTEL
YACHO FOREST - OBSERVATION DECK
Huh?
Yo, yo, yo, yo.
How's it going?
What's up?
I don't see Chinatsu...
That would be because she went on a run.
She said something crazy
like she hadn't trained enough today.
Did she go out by herself?
[Nagisa] Yeah, she said
she'd stay close by, so it's fine.
We just don't have
the stamina to keep up with her.
She's got demonic energy levels.
Okay, got it.
You a fan of hers?
[Taiki internally] "Fan"?
First-year badminton player, right?
Natsu's passionate about her training.
She's always been that way.
[Taiki] Yeah, I know that.
And why are you acting like her boyfriend?
Why're you acting like her boyfriend?
[Taiki] Nagisa!
Huh? Am I?
[Nagisa sighs]
Come on, let's get going.
[Taiki groans internally]
I am 100% not about this guy.
Our Natsu is just as popular
as ever, isn't she?
Well, people would wait
for her after games.
Oh, yeah. I totally remember that.
[Kazuma] There was an upperclassman
I admired like that, too.
Could you not lump me in
with the two of you?
Chinatsu and I are living together!
He used the word "admired."
It's almost like he's saying
what I feel for Chinatsu isn't love.
[footsteps receding]
- [boys laughing]
- What's up with that?
That's what I'm saying, bro.
It's a mystery.
- Dude, no way.
- Makes no sense. Am I right?
Dude, I reek of sweat!
- Man, it's so hot.
- Hoo!
- Um...
- [chuckling]
- [all] Huh?
- Hm?
Hey, have you seen Taiki?
Huh?
When was the last time we saw him, anyway?
He was at the evening session. I think.
[Kyo grunts]
[boy] Maybe he's in the bath.
Oh, got it.
[footsteps running]
UEDA SHIKI HOTEL
[Taiki] I'm genuinely worried
about her running alone at night.
And, coincidentally,
I wanted to go on a run myself.
I am absolutely not,
in any way, stalking Chinatsu!
If it were Hina,
I would've done the same thing.
[wind blowing]
[mellow music playing]
I know that there are a lot of things
I need to spend some time thinking about.
[chuckles softly]
But the more I think about them,
the less sure I am
that those thoughts are my own.
But I feel like you might've added
an extra 30% or so
of feelings for Hina, you know?
[Taiki] Like water
after you've washed a brush in it.
My methodology is to date anybody
who tells me they like me.
[Taiki] Or like mixing together
different drinks at a soda fountain.
[Kazuma] There was an upperclassman
I admired like that, too.
[Taiki] But I think that loving someone
should be more intuitive, right?
And on the topic of my feelings...
I'm pretty sure that
I'm starting to see Hina as a girl.
[Hina] I like you.
[Taiki] After she said that...
That's fine, as long as it reminds you
that I have a crush on you.
It'd be nice to see the guy I like
doing his best.
[Taiki] Little by little.
[inaudible]
[Taiki] And so, the more time passes,
the harder I'm finding it
to answer her confession.
[mellow music ends]
[pants]
BEWARE OF BEARS
[whimpering]
[epic music playing]
[bear charging]
- [roaring]
- [Chinatsu screams]
[epic music ends]
[breath trembling]
[grunts]
[Taiki] Is it true that I feel
some admiration toward Chinatsu?
Sure.
She's a year older than me.
She's beautiful, and popular.
She works hard.
And she's her own person.
Why would she go out running by herself?
[inaudible]
Yes, the two of us have gotten closer...
but as to what's going on in her head,
I still have no idea.
The fact that I do admire her
is making me realize
there's probably still...
some distance between us.
But...
but still...
It's because I admire her
that I want to be with her.
[Chinatsu] Taiki?
[exclaims]
[gasps]
[Chinatsu gasps]
What is going on here?
I was just...
Here's what's going on!
I went into the mountains
to pick vegetables,
and wouldn't you know it, I hurt my ankle!
But then not long after,
this young lady happened to pass by,
and she's graciously carried me this far.
[exclaims softly]
- Well, let me take over.
- Thanks, Taiki.
Luckily, we came across a payphone
while we were walking,
so I called the hotel
and let them know what happened.
Oh, that was probably after I left.
I do feel quite guilty...
causing all this trouble
for you young people.
I'll carry your basket.
- Aren't you tuckered out?
- [Chinatsu] Not at all!
I do exercise every day.
[wind blowing]
[inaudible]
[slow instrumental music playing]
[Taiki] Shall we?
Thanks again.
[Taiki] My favorite color is blue.
My favorite drink is Cola.
That is what I know.
[slow instrumental music ends]
[old woman]
I just can't thank you kids enough.
To sprain my ankle like that,
looks like my age
has finally caught up with me.
Oh, no, that doesn't sound true.
This is what you get
for going into the mountains at night.
I was searching high and low for you,
you know that?
Then I see this young man carrying you.
Good gracious, you're a pain in the neck.
All right, now, Pa, you can it!
Young lady, would you care
for some snacks to take with you?
These are my favorite. They're quite good.
[Chinatsu] Oh, I couldn't.
[old man] Surely we have
something better than those!
[old woman] Right! There is the offering
we got for the Buddhist altar--
Oh, I'll gladly take these!
RICE CRACKERS
[old woman] Your boyfriend
deserves my thanks, too.
[Taiki] Boy--
Oh, no! I'm not her boyfriend!
Aw, man! I got all flustered at that.
Now she's bound to get suspicious.
Should I not have denied it
as hard as I just did?
Then again...
[old woman] Is that right?
I was sure that you'd gotten worried
when she didn't come back,
and so you'd gone out looking for her.
[exclaims softly]
[Taiki groans]
Oh, that? Well...
That was only a coincidence!
I was out running and then saw you two.
About 20% of that is true anyway.
All right, young ones.
I'll drive you back to your hotel.
Good idea, hon.
Oh, no! We don't mind walking.
[old man] It's okay.
Let me do this for you.
Plus, I can't have you walk back
when it's pitch black.
[old man] It's the hotel
up in the mountains, right?
[Taiki] Yes. Ueda Shiki Hotel.
[old man] Yep, you betcha.
Honestly, thank you for your help today.
Ma is always pushing herself to the limit.
Of course. Do take care of yourselves.
[old man] Why, just last month,
no sooner did I tell her to stay home,
she was already out the door.
[peaceful music playing]
[Taiki] Her profile is just...
WELCOME TO THE UEDA SHIKI HOTEL
THANK YOU FOR STAYING WITH US
The both of you
should get straight to bed.
Yes, sir!
Good night!
Good night. Sleep well.
- [door opens]
- Huh?
You've been gone a while.
[Taiki groans]
[Kyo] I see what's going on.
He went after Chinatsu.
And something definitely happened.
[shuttlecock thudding]
Wow! That was a great play!
Come on, Manager!
It isn't fair if you're playing favorites!
[Ayame] But what he just did
was so impressive!
His attack was totally on point.
[boy] Actually, it was a smash.
[Ayame] And on top of that, Muraoka,
you couldn't return
a shot like that before.
You've grown so much as a player!
Manager...
- [Ayame] Keep it up!
- [grunts]
Watch out for that one.
It doesn't mean she's got a crush.
Don't let her fool you.
A real trickster.
The manager is fitting in pretty well.
If that's what you call "fitting in well"!
[Kyo] Trust me,
Muraoka's not taking it to heart.
I mean, I hope you're right.
[Ayame] Hm.
Inota has the best form on the team.
But Yusa's is still better than his.
Oh! They're still practicing.
Hello there.
Rhythmic gymnastics!
Done for today?
We only have weight training left,
so we came back.
And we wanted to pop our heads in.
Hina didn't forget anything?
[Hina] I can hear you!
Oopsie! [chuckles]
Hm.
- We should get a move on.
- Totally.
Good luck with your practice.
[Ayame] Thanksies.
So that worked out.
What did?
You got to see Inomata.
What?
And plus, we see each other all the time.
It's not like I was glad to see him.
[Niina] Right, even when you were looking
all over for him at the hotel.
Honestly, after what happened
at the Cultural Festival,
I really thought they'd get together.
Oh, yeah. Have you heard
about the campfire superstition?
[Hina] That if you confess
to your crush, you'll fall in love?
I know it sounds kinda sketchy.
Yeah, sketchy.
But we're here anyway,
so why don't you try it?
Maybe you'll finally
get an answer from him.
[sighs]
[mellow music playing]
[inaudible]
I won't.
Until Taiki actually
falls in love with me...
I don't need an answer.
[wind blowing]
[mellow music ends]
[closing theme song playing]